When I looked up at the bright sun
I wanted to see you
This sky is the trigger
I miss you so much
Bye, bye, bye
Bye bye bye
Well, I'd like to go home.
This every time. Go around.
But...
I'm going to write it down around here.
It's big.
The person next to me is involved.
I got it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The tour starts today and I look forward to hearing from you.
So let's follow the rules and have fun together. Bye-bye.
Let's go write.
Let's see... I'll write on the right shoulder.
I'll take the right shoulder.
You're going?
You haven't done it yet?
I want to draw a kitten.
Where do you want it?
Did everyone else do it?
Okay, then.
Mentaiko kitten.
Mentaiko.
What?
Laughing.
Wow, you're good.
Wow, that's good.
Mentai Coneko.
Oh, my God, that's perfect.
It's perfect.
Wrap.
Scary self-introduction rap
Scary because it's a person
I'm always scared.
I'm a little scared today
I want to go with you.
I know what you mean.
Kinky little cat.
I have no idea.
Doricon Kitten
Doricon Nekkon.
Doricon Neko
Cute.
Oh, really?
What?
I've been seeing a lot of rabbits lately.
It's not the face.
Go left.
I'll write "I love these shoes.
I love these shoes.
OK.
Fukuoka girl!
Are you seeing this?
I can't see a thing.
Fukuoka girl!
This is Misser.
What do you think?
Long time no see.
It's been a while since I've been to Fukuoka.
I'm glad to be here again.
I'm so happy to be here again.
This is where we toured two years ago.
Already two years ago?
Yeah. What was it?
Well, I was here on the tour.
It's been a long time since I've been back.
It's snowing today.
I'll do my best.
It's so... I mean, everything's changed.
It's all changed.
I wonder if the original is not original
Yes, that remembering.
Hello.
I have to remember...
Pinkman.
I'm Pinkman.
Come practice with me.
Oh, yeah.
Ta-da!
Ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da, ta-da.
Can't you get it up?
Let's go sing some more.
What, can't you speak? Is that okay?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Oh, no, no, no.
Can't you speak up?
There's more to it than that.
It's like a man.
I can't do it. I can't do it at all.
Come on, Mori.
Okay.
I have to go in like this.
Oh, no!
I've never done it with that stick before.First time with the stick.
Yeah, first time.
It's the first time Research's going to do that.
I feel like it's my first and last time.
As far as the inertia...
But the fans, you know, they're surprised.
I'm, I'm, I'm not supposed to do Inatsuki.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Calm down.
Every time you come to kZ형 more than the last.
Next time, it'll be the three-way flow.
What's that? I'm here.
Shake my hand.
We'll use the mats right after sound check.
So if you and your team of managers would like to take the lead on this...
I'd appreciate it.
Okay.
I'll be happy to greet you.
Good morning.
This is Recall Love.
Today is the first day of the tour, so I will do my best.
I look forward to working with you.
Please take care of us.
They prepared Hakata Ramen for us.
I'm heating it up now.
But I'm worried that it might explode because of the egg.
Is that why you're watching?
That's why I'm watching.
I made a hole for it.
Oh, my God!
I can smell the camonoso!
It's pork bones!
What was that?
I've got to eat!
I'll lose my strength!
I'm cold!
What are you doing?
Cup noodles!
There's no way they're cup noodles!
Pork bone ramen!
Wow! Wow! Pork bone ramen?
There are two more!
Eat up!
Wow!
What's best?
Thank you for watching!
Why are you wearing mascara?
You have an eyelash curler?
I don't have an eyelash curler.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
Oh, my God.
What were you doing?
Mascara and curlers.
What? That's not good.
You didn't put it on? Did you just throw it away?
You didn't put it on?
Can we go get it now?
We can go get it now!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Okay, let's practice.
Okay!
Timing's right.
It's the first day of the tour.
Let's have fun.
It's like karaoke, right?
That's right.
Karaoke.
Let's have fun with a karaoke feeling.
Okay, let's go!
Seino
Equal Love!
Today's Equal Love National Tour 2023
TODAY'S YOU ARE TRIGGER
Thank you for coming to TODAY'S YOU ARE TRIGGER
Thank you very much.
Before the show begins
We would like to inform all the audience
Thank you very much for coming.
Please wait at the front of the line until you've been shown the way.
Yes! And so...
Following the daytime performance
We'll be practicing our vocalizations for the evening performance as well.
So, let's practice your voice!
Let's do it!
What? What shall we do?
Well, let's do that one.
Ready?
Hitomi!
What? Let's go with "Mini-Mini-Min"?
Okay! That's it!
Then we'll do it.
When I say "Mirinyah".
Please say "Minya" to everyone!
Here we go!
Mirya!
Mirya!Milya!
Oh! I'm out!
Ready! Mirya!
Mireya!
That's good! You're all so good!
Can we have some Hitomi's version, please?
Here we go.
Hitomi!
Yes! You're all so good!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
The show will begin shortly.
Your voices sound great right now.
Let's have fun with that voice in the show!
Please wait a moment.
This is Hitomi Te, Hitomi Matsu, and Miri Ohtagei.
Words and music by Miho Nakashima, song by Miku Hatsune
On the street where you shouldn't be walking The station is almost there
No, only New Year's Eve was scary
In the morning, if there was goodbye, I'd be in depression
I gazed at hand to hand
Gaze at the adults
I'd wait for a letter, I'd wait for a letter
Just your hand is important to me
Cherry blossoms, look up
All my life I've looked up at my bare hands
The scenery can change just like this
I won't let go
Jaeger the train
He's waiting for you
Come on, you'll never wake up
Just behind that spring
Just then
I'm still here
Someday I want to tell you
I'll tell you someday
I've been looking at them.
I've missed you so much
That's where the real heart shines
Someone special met you
He said he's happy to see you
I opened the comb
Of love and a name
The gift is
I've fallen in love with you
I've grown to love you
Yes, I'm picking up everything in my daily life
My consciousness burns
I've never seen anything like it.
They'll do it again.
Come on, let's go.
I've been dancing up ahead
I'll light up the blue sky
We'll be back tomorrow
Beyond that
I wonder if the sky will bloom
I wish you could hear me
Sunlight enveloped us both in an embrace
Congratulations, you have made it to the last song.
but the song that follows will be the last.
I'm so happy. If we keep going like this, we'll do about 100 more songs.
Yes. So, that's it.
Wow! Oh no!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
Oh, no! What about this one?
Oh! Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
What is this? What is this?
What? It's Ojimaru.
First day.
What?
What is it?
A rock?
Are you kidding me?
What?
Oh, shit!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
That guy! That guy!
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
What?
Gentlemen.
Aah!
Whoa!
Are you okay?
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Where is it?
There's something in here.something is மaat
Something is மaat
-Wow~~~ it disappears already!
Oh, my God!
That's great!
I really don't know anything about it.
The final concert will be held at Nippon Budokan on March 2.
I have always wanted to do a full-capacity show, and I've heard in interviews that all the members have been doing so.
Back then, especially with the Corona Disaster, the audience was half full.
Now that I am able to speak out a little more
I think it is very meaningful for Equal Love to be able to perform at the Nippon Budokan now.
I would like to give the best performance with 10 members.
I hope you will all continue to follow us.
Thank you very much.
I don't think I'm supposed to sing after this.
I'm sure.
May I ask you all to get ready?
Is everything okay?
I'm glad.
Can we take a break?
No, you can't. Before that.
Let's go for it.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I ask you to stand up?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
So, as the first step towards that stage.
I would like to continue on through to the tour finale.
Let's make our dreams bloom together.
Please listen to the song.
Recipe for Smiles
This is really the last song of the tour.
Please listen to it.
Kono Sora wa Tori da
Kono Sora ga Tori da
When I looked up at you as if you had moved
I wanted to see you
I mean je as it is in this sky
I knew from the beginning that you had a lover.
We'll talk about it. The city of flowers.
The radius of the movie is too small
I see the image over and over again.
My own body against the wall
Shaking, the sound of your love.
I'm separating, the sound of your love, the sound of your meanness.
When I looked up at the blue sky.
I haven't forgotten that day.
Everything I see in my eyes
It makes me think of you
My own personal youth
That sky took off
To you
Who do you love
I wonder who it is
Hello! Ray!
Since you've gotten better
I'm picking up love right now
I'll pick up my love now
Even if it wavers
The sky goes on and on
But you
To your back
Back to me
Forever and ever
I have you
Youth
I'm the only one dancing
You're thinking of someone else
Just dance as you like
I'm fine as I am
This love I don't know
Let it be a secret
I'm sure we'll be together
I'll never meet the one I told you about that day
I want to think about it
Thank you for watching.
So, high school students, are you enjoying yourselves today?
It's great. We really enjoyed it too. Thank you very much.
So, what did you think of today, Miryan?
How was it?
Well, I was able to be close to everyone and hear your voices.
And being able to hear everyone's voice...
I used to take it for granted every day.
But now that I'm able to enjoy the experience with you all again, little by little
I felt very happy.
And that factory was the best.
Thank you very much.
How happy I am today, too.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
So, how was it ideal to have the tour in your hometown, Fukuoka?
I was very happy to be able to come back to my hometown with everyone like this, and I am very happy that so many people came.
I am very happy that so many people came to see us.
I am very happy that so many people came to the tour.
I hope that we can continue to deepen our bond with everyone and improve the quality of our performances.
I will do my best to strengthen our bond, improve the quality of the show, and have more fun with everyone.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for the two performances on the first day today.Today we played the first two shows of the tour.
The tour will continue to Miyagi, Osaka, Nagoya, and the final show will be at Nippon Budokan.
Thank you very much for your support.
We will do our best until the final show, so please keep supporting Equal Love.
Please continue to support Equal Love.
Thank you very much.
See you all again!
That's all for now.
Have a good day!
Thank you sollen
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work
Nyonya nyonya nyonya nyonya nyonya nyonya nyonya
Where did you go?
It's over
I'm home.
What's this?
It's over!
Is that it?
Oh, that's a good one.
Yes, it's over.
We're done!
Thank you very much!
Next is Miyagi
Next is Gyutan
Gyutan...
First of all, I haven't eaten any mentaiko.
I would like to eat mentaiko now!
Ho!
Come here, come here, come here, come here
Panda.
Ri-chan is in the middle, right?
You can't stretch your face, can you?
Right here, right?
Are you in?
Here we go.
Here you go.
Mmm-hmm.
Thank you. Thank you.
Here we go.
I'm the only one dressed up.
Lisa, you're not in it.
Here we go.
You can use a mirror.
No, thank you.
Thank you, Lisa.
I knew it. You're so stylish.
That's because I'm Dafaq.
That's because I'm dafuq.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Wow.
Aaaaah!
Who's in?
If Rinna doesn't get in, what's the point?
Let's go.
Are you there? Are you there? Are they all here?
Se-no.
Se-no, Catcher!
Thank you very much.
The first two performances have ended without incident.
Thank you so much to everyone who came and to all of you who gave so much support.
Today was the first time in a long time that I was able to be so close to everyone.
We were also able to perform some parts of the concert with the permission of the audience, so there was a lot of progress in this concert.
We were also very nervous and anxious about performing for the first time with 10 members.
We were also very nervous because it was our first performance with 10 members, and to be honest, we were a little anxious.
But now that it's over, I feel that the fans' voices gave us a lot of strength.
I think there are still many things that we are anxious about, and we are still inexperienced, but we are determined to do our best as a group of 10.
But I think that our will to do our best as 10 members became stronger through this performance today.
The final performance will be held at Nippon Budokan.
We are going to perform at the Nippon Budokan for the final show, so I would like to make it to the third and final show.
I will do my best.
Please continue to follow us.
Thank you very much.